<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- Brazil -->
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_text_vivo_brazil_newfile">We need you to agree that Telefonica Brasil S.A. do not accept any liability for any loss of personal data including, but not limited to Contacts, SMS Content, Account Settings, Multi-media, Photographs &amp; Videos or application / social media settings and or passwords, neither do we accept any liability for any damage caused to the device. Telefonica Brasil S.A. will also gather anonymous data about your appointment and device for the purpose of improving the service, this will include technical information about health checks and diagnostics, this can include the IMEI of the devices we work on. By signing this document, you give Telefonica Brasil S.A. permission to share core data and install third party applications on to your device for the purpose of diagnostics, health checks and data transfers, as approved by Telefonica Brasil S.A, where necessary. We will not store any personal data on our workstations.</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_text_sergio_newfile">Necesitamos que este de acuerdo que no se acepta ninguna responsabilidad por la pérdida de datos personales, incluidos, entre otros, contactos, contenido de SMS, configuración de la cuenta, multimedia, fotografías y videos o configuración de aplicaciones / redes sociales o contraseñas, ni aceptamos cualquier responsabilidad por cualquier daño causado al dispositivo. Se recopilará algunos datos anónimos con el fin de mejorar el servicio, esto incluirá información técnica sobre controles y diagnósticos de salud, esto puede incluir el IMEI de los dispositivos en los que trabajamos. Al firmar este documento, nos otorga permiso para compartir datos básicos e instalar aplicaciones de terceros en su dispositivo con el fin de realizar diagnósticos, verificaciones de estado y transferencias de datos, cuando sea necesario. No almacenaremos ningún dato personal como fotos, videos, música, claves, correos y contactos.</string>

</resources>